Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan) law lectures 1881-1919
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Law School (University of Michigan) law lectures 1881-1919
University of Michigan--Law School.
Transcripts, notes, and outlines of class lectures at the University of Michigan Law School, reproduced and sold by campus area businesses.
88259 Bimu C74 2
13 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection came to the library from a number of source, chief among them the Law School (donor 343 )
The collection is open for research.
The Law Lectures collection represents an "artificial" collection brought together from a number of sources, primarily the Law School but also from individual donors.
The Law Lectures collection contains transcripts, notes, and outlines of class lectures at the University of Michigan Law School for the period 1881-1919. The lectures were produced by various campus area firms, Edwards Bros. being the most prolific publisher. Law Students had the lectures bound for future reference and these bound volumes make up the bulk of the collection.
The collection is physically arranged by the name of the student/collector as shown in the summary contents list below. The source of one volume was unidentifiable, so it is listed under its binder's title "Senior law lectures". The collection also includes a number of unbound lectures, which are stored under the heading "Separate". These unbound lectures sometimes include advertizing for Edwards Bros. lecture service.
The detailed contents list is organized by lecturer and thereunder by lecture title. The name of the student/collector of each lecture is listed in parentheses.
Summary Contents List
Box 1
Babst, Earl D.
Beasly, William Arthur (2 vols.)
Buchanan, Frank Robert (2 vols.)
Box2
Buck, Norman
Cochrane, Alexander Martin (3 vols.)
Box 3
Densmore, Ernest Albert (4 vols.)
Box 4
Erwin, Henry Parsons
Griffin, Franklin Jay
Hammond, Fred David (vol. 1)
Box 5
Hammond, Fred David (vol. 2)
Jewett, Henry Root (3 vols.)
Minor, Donald Ellis (2 vols.)
Box 6
Murray, William Hansen
Plank, Clarence Abrams (2 vols.)
Box 7
Powers, John Ward (2 vols.)
Ringo, Ernest Richard
Sample, George Washington (vol. 1)
Box 8
Sample, George Washington (vol. 2-4)
Box 9
Sample, S.W.
Senior Law Lectures
Separate (Adams-Hutchins)
Box 10
Separate (Kirchner-Wigus)
Box 11
Skillman, Harry Bowne (4 vols.)
Box 12
Storms, Daniel Edward (2 vols.)
Vodrey, William Henry (2 vols.)
Box 13
Weinberg, Adolph (2 vols.)
Weinberg, Max L. (2 vols.)
Subjects:
Edwards Brothers, Inc.; Law.; University of Michigan--Law School.; Lectures and lecturing--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Contributors:
Abbott, Nathan, 1854-1941.; Adams, Henry Carter, 1851-1921.; Adams, R. C.; Adams, Wilbur Christopher.; Ames, Henry Vandenburg, 1865-1935.; Angell, Alexis C. (Alexis Caswell), 1857-1932.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Babst, Earl D., 1870-1967.; Beasly, William Arthur.; Bigelow, Melville Madison, 1846-1921.; Bogle, Thomas Ashford, 1852-1921.; Boudeman, Dallas.; Brewster, James Henry, 1856-1920.; Brown, Henry Billings, 1836-1913.; Buchanan, Frank Robert.; Buck, Norman.; Bunker, Robert Emmet, b. 1848.; Campbell, James V. (James Valentine), 1823-1890.; Champlin, John Wayne, 1831-1901.; Clayberg, John Bertrand, 1853-1921.; Cochrane, Alexander Martin.; Conely, Edwin Forrest, 1847-1902.; Cooley, Thomas McIntyre, 1824-1898.; Davock, Harlow P.; Densmore, Ernest Albert.; Drake, Joseph H. (Joseph Horace), 1860-1947.; Durfee, Edgar N. (Edgar Noble), 1882-; Dwyer, John W. (John William), b. 1865.; Erwin, Henry Parsons, 1881-1953.; Ewell, Marshall Davis, 1844-1928.; Felch, Alpheus, 1804-1896.; Goddard, Edwin C. (Edwin Charles), 1865-1942.; Griffen, Franklin Jay.; Griffin, Levi T. (Levi Thomas), 1837-1906.; Hammond, Fred David.; Hammond, William G. (William Gardiner), 1829-1894.; Herdman, William James, 1848-1906.; High, James L. (James Lambert), 1844-1898.; Howell, William Henry, 1860-1945.; Hudson, Richard, 1845-1915.; Hughes, Thomas Welburn, 1858-1907.; Hurlbut, Wilbur Edson.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Jewett, Henry Root.; Johnson, Elias Finley, 1861-1933.; Kent, Charles A. (Charles Artemis), 1835-1917.; Kirchner, Otto, 1846-1920.; Knowlton, Jerome C. (Jerome Cyril),1850-1916.; Lane, Victor Hugo, 1852-1930.; Lightner, Clarence Ashley, 1862-1938.; Lothrop, George Howard, d. 1896.; Maxwell, Samuel, 1826-1901.; McAlvay, Aaron Vance, 1847-1915.; Mechem, Floyd R. (Floyd Russell), 1858-1928.; Meyers, William J. (William John), 1869-1928; Minor, Donald Ellis.; Mohr, Carl Frank.; Murray, William Hansen.; Page, Lawrence Sherman.; Plank, Clarence Abram.; Post, Louis Freeland, 1849-1928.; Powers, John Ward.; Reed, Frank Fremont, 1857-1926.; Ringo, Ernest Richard.; Rogers, Edward Sidney, 1875-1949.; Rogers, Henry Wade, 1853-1926.; Rood, John R. (John Romain), b. 1868.; Sample, George Washington, 1868-1945.; Sample, S. W.; Sherwood, Benjamin West.; Smalley, Harrison Standish, 1878-1912.; Storms, Daniel Edward.; Sunderland, Edson R. (Edson Read), b. 1874.; Swan, Henry Harrison, 1840-1916.; Thompson, Bradley Martin, 1835-1917.; Vaughan, Victor C. (Victor Clarence), 1851-1929.; Vodrey, William Henry.; Walker, Albert Henry, 1844-1915.; Walker, Charles I. (Charles Irish), 1814-1895.; Waples, Rufus, 1825-1902.; Weinberg, Adolph.; Weinberg, Max L.; Wells, William Palmer, 1831-1891.; Wilgus, Horace L. (Horace La Fayette), 1859-1935.; Wilson, Leroy Allen.
Genre/Form:
Lecture notes.
- [Lecturer Unknown]
  - Admiralty (Box 1)
    (Buchanan, Frank Robert, vol. 1)
  - Agency (Box 1)
    (Buchanan, Frank Robert, vol. 2)
  - Bankruptcy law 1901 (Box 2)
    (Cochrane, Alexander Martin, vol. 2)
  - Common remedial processes (Box 2)
  - Constitutional law (Box 1)
  - Corporations 1898 (Box 8)
    (Sample, George Washington, vol. 2)
  - Courts of the United States 1901 (Box 3)
    (Densmore, Ernest Albert, vol. 2)
  - Covenant for title 1897 (Box 11)
    (Skillman, Harry Bowne, vol. 2)
  - Criminal law 1894 (Box 7)
    (Powers, John Ward, vol. 2)
  - Criminal law 1894 (Box 9)
    (Senior law lectures)
  - Dicey's rules for the selection of the parties ... (Box 8)
  - Examination questions - many topics and years (Box 8)
    (Sample, George Washington, vol. 4)
  - Holmes vs. city of Benton 1894 (Box 6)
    (Plank, Clarence Abram, vol. 2)
  - International law (Box 1)
  - International law 1894 (Box 7)
  - Law of copyrights and trademarks (Box 11)
    (Skillman, Harry Bowne, vol. 3)
  - Outline of contracts (Box 4)
    (Erwin, Henry Parsons)
  - Outline of contracts 1898 (Box 9)
    (Sample, S. W.)
  - Outline of torts (Box 9)
  - Partnership (Box 1)
  - Problems in corporations (Box 8)
  - Quasi contracts 1901 (Box 2)
    (Cochrane, Alexander Martin, vol. 3)
  - Quasi contracts 1903 (Box 4)
  - Questions on federal jurisprudence (Box 8)
  - Second year examination questions 1899 (Box 3)
  - Second year examination questions 1900 (Box 3)
  - Third year examination questions 1901 (Box 7)
    (Ringo, Ernest Richard)
  - Third year examination questions 1902 (Box 7)
  - Third year examination questions 1903 (Box 7)
  - Torts (Box 1)
  - Wills (Box 1)
- Abbott, Nathan
  - Domestic relations 1892 (Box 13)
    (Weinberg, Adolph, vol. 1)
  - Wills 1892 (Box 1)
    (Beasly, William Arthur, vol. 2)
  - Wills 1892 (Box 5)
    (Hammond, Fred David, vol. 2)
  - Wills 1892 (Box 7)
    (Powers, John Ward, vol. 1)
  - Wills 1892 (Box 12)
    (Storms, Daniel Edward, vol. 1)
- Adams, Henry Carter
  - Labor problem and the monopoly problem 1894 (Box 13)
    (Weinberg, Max L., vol. 1)
  - Principles of the science of finance 1894 (Box 13)
  - Transportation problem 1894 (Box 4)
    (Griffen, Franklin Jay)
  - Transportation problem 1894 (Box 13)
- Adams, R.C.
  - History of the development of industrial society 1901 (Box 4)
- Adams, Wilbur Christopher
  - Outline of Wilgus' Corporation cases (Box 9)
    (Separate)
- Ames, Herman Vandenburg
  - American constitutional history 1894 (Box 4)
  - American constitutional history 1894 (Box 13)
- Angell, Alexis Caswell
  - Constitutional law (Box 4)
  - Constitutional law (Box 13)
    (Weinberg, Max L., vol. 2)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 1)
    (Babst, Earl D.)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 5)
    (Jewett, Henry Root, vol. 3)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 6)
    (Murray, William Hansen)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 6)
    (Plank, Clarence Abram, vol. 1)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 7)
  - Constitutional law 1894 (Box 9)
  - Constitutional law 1895 (Box 12)
    (Vodrey, William Henry, vol. 2)
  - Constitutional law 1896 (Box 5)
    (Minor, Donald Ellis, vol. 1)
  - Domestic relations 1894 (Box 5)
    (Jewett, Henry Root, vol. 1)
  - Domestic relations 1895 (Box 12)
    (Vodrey, William Henry, vol. 1)
  - Domestic relations 1896 (Box 11)
    (Skillman, Harry Bowne, vol. 1)
- Angell, James Burrill
  - History of treaties (Box 1)
  - History of treaties 1894 (Box 4)
  - History of treaties 1894 (Box 13)
  - History of treaties 1902 (Box 4)
  - History of treaties 1902 (Box 8)
    (Sample, George Washington, vol. 1)
  - Public international law (Box 4)
  - Public international law 1894 (Box 13)
  - Public international law 1902 (Box 8)
- Beasly, William Arthur
  - Remedies for wrongs incident to private corp... 1892 (Box 1)
- Bigelow, Melville Madison
  - Insurance (Box 9)
  - Insurance 1901 (Box 8)
  - Insurance 1902 (Box 3)
    (Densmore, Ernest Albert, vol. 3)
  - Law of insurance (Box 1)
  - Law of insurance (Box 1)
  - Law of insurance (Box 5)
  - Law of insurance 1894 (Box 5)
    (Jewett, Henry Root, vol. 2)
  - Law of insurance 1894 (Box 13)
  - Law of insurance 1898 (Box 2)
  - Law of insurance 1898 (Box 6)
    (Page, Lawrence Shearman, vol. 3)
  - Law of insurance 1898 (Box 8)
  - Law of insurance 1898 (Box 11)
  - Torts 1891 (Box 4)
    (Hammond, Fred David, vol. 1)
  - Wills (Box 1)
    (Beasly, William Arthur, vol. 1)
- Bogle, Thomas Ashford
  - Stephen's rules of pleading (Box 8)
- Boudeman, Dallas
  - Michigan statute law 1902 (Box 3)
- Brewster, James Henry
  - Conveyancing 1897 (Box 11)
  - Conveyancing 1898 (Box 6)
  - Conveyancing 1899 (Box 8)
    (Sample, George Washington, vol. 3)
  - Conveyancing 1900 (Box 2)
  - Law of conveyancing 1902 (Box 3)
    (Densmore, Ernest Albert, vol. 4)
- Brown, Henry Billings
  - Admiralty (Box 1)
  - Admiralty and maritime law 1891 (Box 5)
- Bunker, Robert Emmet
  - Bills and notes 1902 (Box 4)
  - Bills and notes 1902 (Box 9)
  - Bills and notes 1903 (Box 2)
    (Cochrane, Alexander Martin, vol. 1)
  - Equity jurisprudence cases 1902 (Box 3)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1902 (Box 3)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1904 (Box 2)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1904 (Box 7)
  - Suretyship (Box 7)
- Campbell, James Valentine
  - Criminal law 1881 (Box 1)
    (Buck, Norman)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1881 (Box 1)
- Champlin, John Wayne
  - Corporations 1895 (Box 9)
  - Corporations 1895 (Box 12)
  - Municipal corporations (Box 1)
  - Municipal corporations 1892 (Box 5)
  - Municipal corporations 1892 (Box 7)
  - Municipal corporations 1892 (Box 12)
  - Municipal corporations 1892 (Box 13)
    (Weinberg, Adolph, vol. 2)
  - Municipal corporations 1894 (Box 5)
  - Municipal corporations 1894 (Box 6)
  - Municipal corporations 1894 (Box 7)
  - Private corporations 1892 (Box 1)
  - Private corporations 1892 (Box 5)
  - Private corporations 1892 (Box 7)
  - Private corporations 1892 (Box 12)
  - Private corporations 1892 (Box 13)
  - Private corporations 1894 (Box 5)
  - Private corporations 1894 (Box 6)
  - Private corporations 1894 (Box 7)
  - Torts 1892 (Box 13)
  - Torts 1894 (Box 5)
  - Torts 1894 (Box 6)
  - Torts 1894 (Box 9)
  - Torts 1895 (Box 11)
  - Torts 1895 (Box 12)
- Clayberg, John Bertrand
  - Mining law (Box 1)
  - Mining law (Box 2)
  - Mining law (Box 5)
  - Mining law 1894 (Box 13)
  - Mining law 1898 (Box 6)
  - Mining law 1898 (Box 11)
    (Skillman, Harry Bowne, vol. 4)
  - Mining law 1899 (Box 8)
- Conley, Edwin Forrest
  - Agency 1892 (Box 6)
  - Agency 1892 (Box 13)
  - Constitutional law 1892 (Box 5)
  - Constitutional law 1892 (Box 7)
  - Constitutional law 1892 (Box 12)
  - Constitutional law 1892 (Box 13)
  - Partnership 1892 (Box 1)
  - Partnership 1892 (Box 6)
  - Partnership 1892 (Box 13)
- Cooley, Thomas McIntyre
  - Bailments 1881 (Box 1)
  - Domestic relations 1881 (Box 1)
  - Interstate commerce law (Box 1)
  - Interstate commerce law (Box 13)
  - Interstate commerce law 1891 (Box 5)
  - Webster-Hayne debate 1895 (Box 9)
  - Webster-Hayne debate 1895 (Box 12)
- Davock, Harlow P.
  - Bankruptcy law 1902 (Box 3)
- Drake, Joseph Horace
  - Development of the Roman constitution 1901 (Box 9)
  - History of Roman law 1901 (Box 8)
- Durfee, Edgar Noble
  - Equity (cases) (Box 9)
- Dwyer, John William
  - Courts of the United States 1897 (Box 8)
- Ewell, Marshall Davis
  - Medical jurisprudence 1891 (Box 1)
  - Medical jurisprudence 1891 (Box 4)
  - Medical jurisprudence 1894 (Box 7)
  - Medical jurisprudence 1894 (Box 13)
- Felch, Alpheus
  - Real estate 1881 (Box 1)
- Goddard, Edwin Charles
  - Elementary law (Box 9)
  - Elementary law 1904 (Box 4)
- Griffin, Levi Thomas
  - Common law pleading and civil procedure 1896 (Box 11)
  - Evidence (Box 1)
  - Evidence (Box 1)
  - Evidence 1892 (Box 1)
  - Evidence 1892 (Box 5)
  - Evidence 1892 (Box 7)
  - Evidence 1892 (Box 12)
  - Evidence 1892 (Box 13)
  - Evidence 1894 (Box 5)
  - Evidence 1894 (Box 6)
  - Evidence 1894 (Box 6)
  - Evidence 1894 (Box 7)
  - Evidence 1896 (Box 5)
    (Minor, Donald Ellis, vol. 2)
  - Evidence 1896 (Box 12)
  - Evidence 1898 (Box 11)
  - Federal jurisprudence (Box 1)
  - Federal jurisprudence (Box 4)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1892 (Box 5)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1892 (Box 7)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1892 (Box 12)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1892 (Box 13)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1894 (Box 1)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1894 (Box 5)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1894 (Box 6)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1894 (Box 7)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1894 (Box 9)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1895 (Box 5)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1895 (Box 12)
  - Personal property (Box 1)
  - Personal property (Box 4)
  - Personal property 1892 (Box 1)
  - Personal property 1892 (Box 13)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 1)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 5)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 5)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 6)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 6)
  - Personal property 1894 (Box 9)
  - Personal property 1895 (Box 12)
  - Personal property 1896 (Box 11)
  - Pleading and practice 1891 (Box 4)
  - Pleading and practice 1892 (Box 1)
  - Pleading and practice 1892 (Box 9)
  - Pleading and practice 1892 (Box 13)
  - Pleading and practice 1894 (Box 1)
  - Pleading and practice 1894 (Box 5)
  - Pleading and practice 1894 (Box 5)
  - Pleading and practice 1894 (Box 6)
- Hammond, Fred David
  - Modern uses of streets (Box 5)
- Hammond, William G.
  - History of the common law (Box 13)
- Herdman, William James
  - Neurology, electrology and railway injuries 1899 (Box 8)
- High, James Lambert
  - Equity 1890 (Box 4)
  - Injunction and receivers 1894 (Box 13)
  - Injunction and receivers 1895 (Box 12)
  - Injunctions and receivers 1894 (Box 5)
  - Injunctions and receivers 1897 (Box 6)
  - Injunctions and receivers 1897 (Box 11)
- Howell, William Henry
  - Medico-legal microscopy 1891 (Box 5)
- Hudson, Richard
  - Comparative constitutional law (Box 4)
  - Comparative constitutional law 1894 (Box 13)
- Hughes, Thomas Welburn
  - Outline of criminal law 1898 (Box 9)
  - Outline of evidence (Box 8)
- Hurlburt, Wilbur Edson
  - Synoptical outline of Holland's Elements ... 1898 (Box 8)
  - Synoptical outline of Holland's Elements of jur... 1898 (Box 6)
  - Synoptical outline of Holland's Elements of jur... 1898 (Box 11)
- Hutchins, Harry Burns
  - Equity jurisprudence 1895 (Box 11)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1895 (Box 12)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1896 (Box 5)
  - Equity jurisprudence (cases) 1895 (Box 9)
  - Equity jurisprudence, jr. 1899 (Box 8)
  - Equity jurisprudence, jr. 1901 (Box 3)
  - Equity jurisprudence, jr. 1903 (Box 2)
  - Equity jurisprudence, jr. 1904 (Box 9)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1900 (Box 8)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1901 (Box 2)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1902 (Box 3)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1904 (Box 7)
  - Law of real property including easements 1887 (Box 9)
  - Medical jurisprudence (Box 9)
- Johnson, Elias Finley
  - Abstracts of cases in injunctions and receivers (Box 11)
  - Abstracts of cases in injunctions and receivers 1897 (Box 6)
  - Medical jurisprudence 1900 (Box 8)
- Kent, Charles Artemas
  - Practice and pleading 1881 (Box 1)
- Kirchner, Otto
  - Husband and wife 1900 (Box 3)
    (Densmore, Ernest Albert, vol. 1)
  - Husband and wife 1902 (Box 2)
  - Marital relations 1894 (Box 1)
  - Marital relations 1894 (Box 5)
  - Marital relations 1894 (Box 5)
  - Marital relations 1896 (Box 11)
  - Marital relations 1896 (Box 12)
  - Marital relations 1899 (Box 9)
  - Preparation for trial 1894 (Box 5)
  - Preparation for trial 1894 (Box 6)
  - Preparation for trial 1895 (Box 9)
  - Private corporations 1891 (Box 4)
  - Private international law 1894 (Box 5)
  - Private international law 1894 (Box 6)
  - Private international law 1894 (Box 6)
  - Private international law 1894 (Box 7)
  - Private international law 1894 (Box 9)
  - Private international law 1895 (Box 5)
  - Private international law 1895 (Box 12)
  - Private international law 1898 (Box 6)
  - Private international law 1898 (Box 11)
  - Private international law 1899 (Box 8)
  - Private international law 1900 (Box 2)
  - Private international law 1902 (Box 3)
- Knowlton, Jerome Cyril
  - Bailments (Box 1)
  - Bailments (Box 4)
  - Bailments 1892 (Box 1)
  - Bailments 1892 (Box 1)
  - Bailments 1892 (Box 12)
    (Storms, Daniel Edward, vol. 2)
  - Bailments 1892 (Box 13)
  - Bailments 1894 (Box 5)
  - Bailments 1894 (Box 6)
  - Bailments and carriers 1897 (Box 11)
  - Closing address to law class of '94 1894 (Box 6)
  - Common carriers (Box 1)
  - Common carriers (Box 1)
  - Common carriers 1892 (Box 1)
  - Common carriers 1892 (Box 5)
  - Common carriers 1892 (Box 13)
  - Common carriers 1894 (Box 5)
  - Common carriers 1894 (Box 6)
  - Contract law 1903 (Box 10)
  - Contracts (Box 1)
  - Contracts (Box 13)
  - Contracts 1892 (Box 12)
  - Contracts 1894 (Box 1)
  - Contracts 1894 (Box 5)
  - Contracts 1894 (Box 6)
  - Contracts 1900 (Box 3)
  - Criminal law (Box 13)
  - Criminal law 1895 (Box 11)
  - Criminal law 1895 (Box 12)
  - Criminal law 1896 (Box 5)
  - Criminal law 1898 (Box 9)
  - Criminal law 1899 (Box 3)
  - Criminal law 1902 (Box 2)
  - Criminal law and procedure 1894 (Box 5)
  - Criminal law and procedure 1894 (Box 6)
  - Criminal law and statutory crime 1892 (Box 1)
  - Criminal law and statutory crime 1892 (Box 1)
  - Criminal law and statutory crimes 1892 (Box 5)
  - Criminal law and statutory crimes 1892 (Box 7)
  - Criminal law and statutory crimes 1892 (Box 12)
  - Jewish institutions 1894 (Box 10)
  - Jewish institutions including the trial of Jesus.. 1894 (Box 8)
  - Public corporations 1898 (Box 6)
  - Public corporations 1898 (Box 11)
  - Quasi-contracts 1898 (Box 9)
  - Railway law 1898 (Box 11)
  - Railway law 1900 (Box 2)
  - Railway law 1900 (Box 8)
  - Trial of Jesus (Box 2)
- Lane, Victor Hugo
  - Bailments and carriers 1899 (Box 8)
  - Bailments and carriers 1902 (Box 10)
  - Evidence 1902 (Box 2)
  - Evidence 1902 (Box 10)
  - Evidence 1904 (Box 10)
  - Extraordinary legal remedies 1900 (Box 8)
  - Extraordinary legal remedies 1901 (Box 2)
  - Extraordinary legal remedies 1901 (Box 3)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1899 (Box 8)
  - Federal jurisprudence 1901 (Box 3)
  - Personal property 1902 (Box 2)
  - Practical instruction 1897 (Box 11)
  - Practical instruction in the trial of causes 1900 (Box 2)
  - Practical instruction in the trial of causes 1900 (Box 3)
  - Practical instructions 1899 (Box 8)
  - Sales 1899 (Box 9)
  - Sales 1902 (Box 10)
  - Sales 1903 (Box 4)
  - Sales [i.e. Personal property] 1901 (Box 3)
- Lightner, Clarenc Ashley
  - Medical jurisprudence 1915 (Box 10)
- Lothrop, George Howard
  - Patent law (Box 1)
  - Patent law (Box 5)
  - Patent law 1894 (Box 4)
  - Patent law 1894 (Box 9)
  - Patent law 1894 (Box 13)
- Maxwell, Samuel
  - Code pleading 1890 (Box 4)
- McAlvay, Aaron Vance
  - Domestic relations 1899 (Box 9)
  - Domestic relations 1900 (Box 3)
  - Domestic relations 1902 (Box 2)
  - Equity jurisprudence, sr. 1897 (Box 11)
  - Wills and administration 1899 (Box 3)
  - Wills and administration 1899 (Box 8)
  - Wills and administration 1901 (Box 2)
- Mechem, Floyd Russell
  - Agency (Box 9)
  - Agency 1894 (Box 5)
  - Agency 1894 (Box 6)
  - Agency 1896 (Box 11)
  - Agency 1898 (Box 3)
  - Agency 1901 (Box 10)
  - Damages 1895 (Box 5)
  - Damages 1895 (Box 11)
  - Damages 1895 (Box 12)
  - Damages 1898 (Box 8)
  - Domestic relations 1894 (Box 6)
  - Law of partnership 1893 (Box 6)
  - Partnership 1899 (Box 8)
  - Partnership 1902 (Box 10)
  - Wills 1894 (Box 5)
  - Wills 1894 (Box 6)
  - Wills 1894 (Box 6)
  - Wills and administration 1895 (Box 12)
  - Wills and administration 1897 (Box 8)
  - Wills and administration 1897 (Box 11)
  - Wills and administration of estates 1893 (Box 13)
- Meyers, William John
  - Outline of Blackstone (Box 9)
  - Outline of Bliss on code pleading (Box 8)
  - Outline of Burdick on sales (Box 9)
  - Outline of Cooley on torts (Box 9)
  - Outline of real property (Blackstone) 1898 (Box 9)
- Mohr, Carl Frank
  - Liability for negligence of a servant ... 1900 (Box 8)
- Post, Louis Freeland
  - Single tax (Box 6)
- Reed, Frank Fremont
  - Law of copyrights and trademarks 1899 (Box 8)
  - Law of literary property and copyright (Box 10)
- Rogers, Edward Sidney
  - Law of copyright (Box 10)
- Rogers, Henry Wade
  - Criminal law (Box 1)
  - Domestic relations (Box 1)
  - Domestic relations 1891 (Box 4)
  - Domestic relations 1891 (Box 12)
  - Roman law (Box 5)
- Rood, John Romain
  - Outline of common remedial processes (Box 8)
- Sample, George Washington
  - Was the case of Brown vs. Chicago...decided correctly 1901 (Box 8)
- Sherwood, Benjamin West
  - Outline of Cooley on taxation, 2d. ed. (Box 8)
  - Outline of Greenleaf 1901 (Box 3)
  - Outline of Greenleaf, 16th edition--Wigmore (Box 8)
- Smalley, Harrison Standish
  - Corporations 1908 (Box 10)
- Sunderland, Edson Read
  - Brief Sunderland's cases code pleading (Box 10)
  - Materials for the study of ... procedure 1917 (Box 10)
- Swan, Henry Harrison
  - Admiralty 1899 (Box 8)
  - Admiralty law 1894 (Box 13)
  - Admiralty law 1895 (Box 11)
- Thompson, Bradley Martin
  - Assignments 1900 (Box 2)
  - Assignments 1902 (Box 3)
  - Assignments for the benefit of creditors 1898 (Box 6)
  - Assignments for the benefit of creditors 1898 (Box 8)
  - Assignments for the benefit of creditors 1898 (Box 11)
  - Bankruptcy law 1901 (Box 8)
  - Equity jurisprudence (Box 1)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1892 (Box 1)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1892 (Box 5)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1892 (Box 7)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1892 (Box 12)
  - Equity jurisprudence 1892 (Box 13)
  - Equity pleading and practice (Box 10)
  - Equity pleading and practice 1903 (Box 2)
  - Fixtures and easements 1892 (Box 10)
  - Fixtures and easements 1901 (Box 3)
  - Fixtures and easements 1903 (Box 10)
  - Landlord and tenant (Box 1)
  - Landlord and tenant 1892 (Box 1)
  - Landlord and tenant 1892 (Box 5)
  - Landlord and tenant 1892 (Box 12)
  - Landlord and tenant 1892 (Box 13)
  - Landlord and tenant 1896 (Box 5)
  - Landlord and tenant 1896 (Box 11)
  - Landlord and tenant 1896 (Box 12)
  - Landlord and tenant 1900 (Box 8)
  - Landlord and tenant 1901 (Box 3)
  - Mortgages 1896 (Box 5)
  - Mortgages 1896 (Box 6)
  - Mortgages 1896 (Box 11)
  - Mortgages 1896 (Box 12)